<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobile Treasure Hunt</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="clue_solved">Clue Solved</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_completed">Treasure Hunt Completed</string>
    <string name="clue">Clue</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_start">Treasure Hunt Start</string>
    <string name="bean_clue">This Chicago landmark is a sculpture where tourists from around the world come to take photos of their reflection.</string>
    <string name="wrigley_clue">This historic Chicago landmark is one of the oldest standing structures in its structure type.</string>
    <string name="bean_hint">It is often to referred to using a legume-themed name.</string>
    <string name="wrigley_hint">Its \"structure type\" is baseball stadiums.</string>
    <string name="bean_description">Cloud Gate is a sculpture created by Anish Kapoor, located in Chicago\'s Millennium Park. Its design was inspired by liquid mercury, and the surface of the sculpture reflects and distorts Chicago\'s skyline.</string>
    <string name="wrigley_description">Wrigley Field opened in 1914, under the name Weeghman Park. The Wrigley Company purchased the Cubs in 1921 and renamed the stadium to Wrigley Field in 1927. Only Fenway Park is older.</string>
    <string name="hint">Hint</string>
    <string name="found_it">Found It!</string>
    <string name="quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="congrats">Congratulations! You have solved the treasure hunt! Check out your time at the bottom of the screen!</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="rules">In this treasure hunt, you will be presented with two clues, each with optional hints if you are stuck. Your task is to go to the location corresponding to each clue, and then click the \"Found It!\" button on that clue\'s page. Once you have successfully found the locations for both clues, you will have solved the treasure hunt! Act fast, because you will be timed! When you\'re ready, click the \"Start\" button.</string>
    <string name="loc_not_granted">Locations Permissions Not Granted</string>
    <string name="alert_body">This app requires location data to operate properly. Please click Confirm or Dismiss to close the app. If you want to use this app, please update your location services permission in the settings for this app.</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="toast_alert">Location permission not granted</string>
    <string name="incorrect_location_alert_title">Incorrect Location</string>
    <string name="incorrect_location_alert_body">You are at an incorrect location for this clue. Please try a different location. Click either \"Confirm\" or \"Dismiss\" to close this notification.</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_start_page_title">Treasure Hunt Start</string>
    <string name="clues">Clues</string>
    <string name="clue_solved_title">Clue Solved</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_completed_title">Treasure Hunt Completed</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_elapsed_time">"Total Treasure Hunt Elapsed Time: "</string>
</resources>